Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
- Series XI. Pesticides
  - Pesticide Education Packet - Cornell Migrant Program, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Pesticide Education Packet, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Series XII. Housing
  - Housing for Migrant Farmworkers (Cornell), 1953 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - To House the Migrant - New York State Migrant Center (Geneseo), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Migrant Shelter - A Housing Dilemma (New York State), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Hope Village/Waynco Housing Opportunities, 1972-1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - CASH (Community Action In Self-Help), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - CASH (Community Action In Self-Help), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - CASH (Community Action In Self-Help), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - CASH (Community Action In Self-Help), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - CASH (Community Action In Self-Help), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Cohn Foundation/CASH, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - How Well Are We Housed? - U.S. Dept. Housing and Urban Development, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cooperative Housing for Rural America, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Hired Farmworker Housing - USDA, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - A Look at Farmworker Housing in California, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative Housing (Including Hope Village) - Federal Home Loan Bank, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Homes of the Brave - Rural America, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Rural Advisory Group, New York State Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Migrant Labor Camps (New York State), 1982-1998 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Migrant Services Program (Housing) - California, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Farm Labor Housing in New York State - RYNFO (Rural Opportunities), 1985 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Farm Labor Housing, 1985-2005 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Inspections of Labor Camps by New York State Department of Labor, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Farm Labor Camp Visitation Right - Attorney General (New York) Robert Abrams, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Migrant Labor Camps - Revision of Regulations (New York State), 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Housing and Home Environment - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1991-1995 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Identifying American Households at Risk of Housing Problems, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Employee Housing: A Guide for Farm Employers - Kay Embrey, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Farmworker Housing Demonstration Program - Rural Opportunities, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Migrant Labor Camps - Revision of Regulations, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Migrant Labor Camps - Revision of Regulations, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Farm Labor Camps - Pennsylvania, Oregon (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Wayne County (New York State) Migrant Camps by Town, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Community Economic Development Finance - Krys Cail, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Farmworker Housing in New York State - Rural Opportunities, Inc., 2000 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - New York State Farming Housing Symposium, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Series XIII. Parent Advisory Council
  - Faith Richardson - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) Guidelines - Faith Richardson (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Parent Advisory Councils - Tutorial Outreach Programs - Faith Richardson, 1978-1986 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1981-1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson (1), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson (2), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Parent Advisory Council (New York State Migrant Education) - Faith Richardson, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - New York State Title I Committee of Practitioners - Faith Richardson, 1996-1999 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Farmworker Oral Histories - Faith (Fay) Richardson, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Parent Advisory Council - East Bloomfield (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Parent Advisory Council - Oswego (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Multicultural Library (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Home-School Issues Workshop, 1993-06-12-1993-06-13 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Parent Advisory Committee Notebook - Faith Richardson (1) (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Parent Advisory Committee Notebook - Faith Richardson (2) (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Apprentice Training Notebook - Faith Richardson (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Series XIV. Migrant Museum Exhibit
  - Coming Up on the Season Museum Exhibit, 1995-1999 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Coming Up on the Season Museum Exhibit, 2002-2005 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Coming Up on the Season - NEH Events, Exhibitions and Programs, 2000-2004 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Initial Script (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Exhibit Plan, Content, Final (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Consultant Agreements, 1996-2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Website: Nick Dunfey, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Equipment and Materials (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Traveling Museum Exhibit - Planning Grant, 1994-1996 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Museum Exhibit Background Ideas (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Kheel Center, Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Coming Up on the Season - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Reports for NEH, 1998-2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Final NEH Report (1), 2002 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Final NEH Report (2), 2002 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Final NEH Report (3), 2002 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Original Photographs (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Selected Photos of the Exhibit (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Exhibit Teachers' Resources PDF (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Newman's Own Foundation, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Rockefeller Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Coming Up on the Season - New York State Council on the Arts, 1999-2002 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Exhibit Brochure (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Exhibit Family Gallery Guide (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Media DVD (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Up the Road on the Season - Ruth Mott Fund (not funded), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Up the Road on the Season - N.J. Council for the Humanities (not funded), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Up the Road on the Season - New York Council for the Humanities (not funded), 1997 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Fund for Folk Culture (not funded), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Proposals Not Funded, 1997-2000 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Upstate History Alliance Award, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Publicity (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Hammond Museum, 2001-2003 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Tompkins County Museum, 2000-2002 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Visitors' Log (New Jersey) (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Coming Up on the Season - New Jersey Historical Society, 2001-2004 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Coming Up on the Season - National Heritage Museum, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Long Island Museum, 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Museum of American Financial History, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Rubenstein Museum, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Coming Up on the Season - Yager Museum, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Faculty Fellows in Service (Student Translators), 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Transcription for Coming Up on the Season Interviews, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Audio Interview Tapes for Coming Up on the Season (Box 35)
- Series XV. Rural Opportunities
  - Program Funding, Inc. - Incorporation Papers, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - A Brief History of Bureau of Program Funding - PFI - RYNFO (ROI) (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - ROI Correspondence - Stuart J. Mitchell, 1979-2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - PFI (ROI) Correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Program for Migrants...PFI - Stephen P. Johnson, 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Farmworker Justice - Annual Reports (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 1975-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 1982-1984, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 1990-1993 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - ROI Annual Reports, 2001, 2002, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Rural Housing Action Co. (RHAC) - Affiliate of ROI, Creation, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - RHAC (ROI), 1986-1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - RHAC (ROI), 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - RHAC (ROI), 1997-2000 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - RHAC, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - RHAC, 2003-2005 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Rural Housing Opportunities Co. (RHOC) - ROI, 1992-2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - RHAC Development Co. (ROI), 1985-1997 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Frameworks (ROI Affiliate) Initial Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Frameworks, 1985-1988 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Farmworker Housing Company of New York (ROI) Creation, 1991-1996 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - ROI and Housing Opportunities, Inc. (HOP) Merger, 2004-2005 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Program Funding (ROI), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Program Funding (ROI), 1977 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Program Funding (ROI), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Program Funding (ROI), 1979 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - ROI (Rural Opportunities, Inc.), 1981-12 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ROI, 1982-06 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - ROI, 1982-03 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - ROI, 1982-10 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - ROI, 1982-12 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - ROI, 1984-1986 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - ROI, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - ROI, 1988-03, 1988-07 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - ROI, 1988-08, 1988-10 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - ROI, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Summary of Farmworker Caucus Issues 1972-1989, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - ROI, 1990-03, 1990-06 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - ROI, 1990-08 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - ROI, 1991-02, 1991-04, 1991-10 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Rural Opportunities, Inc. Board Resource Manual, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - ROI, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - ROI, 1993-01, 1993-07, 1993-10 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - ROI, 1994-01, 1994-06, 1991-10 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Farm Labor - A Violation of Civil Rights - ROI, Oct. 1994, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - ROI, 1995-03, 1995-07, 1995-10 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - ROI, 1996-06, 1996-10 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - ROI, 1997-01, 1997-04 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - ROI, 1998-04, 1988-10 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - ROI, 1999-01, 1999-04, 1999-07 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ROI, 2000-03-08 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - ROI, 2000-10 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ROI Advocacy Trip, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - ROI, 2001-04-28 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - ROI, 2001-08, 2001-10 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - ROI, 2002-03, 2002-08, 2002-10 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - ROI, 2003-03, 2003-07, 2003-10 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - ROI, 2004-03, 2004-07, 2004-10 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - ROI - Pennsylvania 25th Anniversary, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - ROI, 2005-03, 2005-07 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - ROI, 2005-10 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ROI Board Manual, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Public Policy - ROI, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - ROI, 2006-03 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - ROI, 2006-07, 2006-10 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Series XVI. Working Together, Rural and Migrant Ministry
  - Working Together, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Working Together photos - Tribute to Senator Olga Mendez at SUNY Brockport (Box 39, Folder 1A)
  - Working Together, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Working Together, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Working Together, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Working Together (New York State), 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Working Together, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Working Together, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Working Together, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Working Together (New York State), 1999-2001 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Working Together (New York State), 2002-2005 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry Project, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - The Voice of Farmworkers (Rural and Migrant Ministry), 2000 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Rural and Migrant Ministry, 2000-05 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Sowing Seeds for Justice (RMM's 25th Anniversary), 2006 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Coins of Change (Rural and Migrant Ministry) - New York State (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Harvester - Rural and Migrant Ministry (New York State) (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Series XVII. Articles Concerning Farmworkers and Migrant Issues
  - Haitian Migrant Farmworkers (see also King Ferry Camp), 1987 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - King Ferry (New York) Migrant Labor (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Migrants' Misfortune - SUNY News (State University of New York), 1982 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Migrants: Exploited, Neglected and Discriminated Against, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Losing Ground - Black Farmers in America (Rural America), 1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - NY Times Article - "As Economy Booms, Migrant Workers' Housing Worsens", 1998-06 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Articles, 1981-1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Articles, 1990-2004 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Articles related to Cornell Migrant Program, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1955-1982 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1992-1997 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Articles: Migrant Farmworkers, 2002-2006 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Border Issues - Local Impact, 2002-04-15 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Campus Migrant Program, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Brockport, no date (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Changing Labor Force (To Latino) Upstate, 1989-10 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Changing Labor Force (To Latino) Downstate, 2002-01-27, 2002-05-12 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Children, 1988-10-16, 2001-09-16 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Churches - Rochester area, 1991-07-18 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "Dirt Poor" - SUNY Article, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Drug Arrests, 1986-10-18, 1987-01, 1989-10-28, 1990-3-06, 1990-04-03 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Eastern New York Growers- News Stories, 1998-07-02, 1989-06-01, 2000-09-01 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Eastern New York - Workers and Life, 1990-10-21; 1995-07-13 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Editorials by Growers and FBA, 1987-09-27, 1997-05-30, 1997-09-28, 1997-11-17, 1998-04-08, 1999-03-11, 2003-11-10, 2004-01-15 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Editorials By Workers and Advocates, 1987, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Editorials and Letters to Editor-Local, 2002-03-26, 2002-04-18 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Emerging Hispanic Communities Series- Rochester Area, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Equality and Rights - NY, 2003, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Farm Labor - 1980's articles, 1980-12, 1982-11 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Farmworkers - National News Articles, 1983, 1989-1994 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - FLSNY, 2002-09 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Haitians, 1983, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Health, 1988-04-08, 2001-03-13 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Housing, 1987, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, 1991-10-24 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Ithaca, 1987, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Long Island and FWS, 1989-01-26 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Mechanization, 1984-03-18 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Oswego Area, 1987, 2002, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Raids - Immigration, no date (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Trade With Mexico - Local Impact, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - WNY Growers, Farms, Agri-Business, 1986, 1991, 1992, 2003, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Wayne County Farms - Agri-Business, 1989, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Wayne County Workers and Life, 1978, 1985, 1989, 2002, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Western New York - Ag Labor Supply, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Western New York Workers News Stories, 1983, 1987, 1993, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Literary Program Articles, 1988-07 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - WCMAP, 1985, 1988, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Talbert Hall, 1992-02-06 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Ymose St. Fleur- Student, 2000-05-10, 2005-08-12 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - News Article - Misc, 1985-1990 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - News Articles - Misc, 1980-2004 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- Series XVIII. Estimates of Numbers of Farmworkers
  - A Census of Migrants in Eight Western New York State Counties in 1968, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Estimate of the Number of Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Where Have All the Farmworkers Gone? - Rural America, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - The Hired Farm Working Force of 1976 (USDA), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Farm Labor in New York State: A Statistical Overview (Dennis U. Fisher), 1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - The Hired Farm Working Force of 1977 (USDA), 1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - The Hired Farm Working Force of 1979 (USDA), 1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Hired Farmworkers - Background and Trends for the Eighties (USDA), 1981 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Hired Farm Labor Data from the Decennial Census (USDA), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - The Hired Farm Working Force of 1981 (USDA), 1983 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Counting Hired Farmworkers (USDA) (1), 1984 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Counting Hired Farmworkers (USDA) (2), 1984 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Labor Data Sources: An Update (USDA), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - The Population and Labor Force of New York: 1990-2050, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey (No. 2, U.S. D.O.L), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Trends in the Hired Farmworker Force, 1945-1987 (USDA), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - 1987 Census of Agriculture (U.S. Dept. of Commerce), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - The Agricultural Work Force of 1987 (USDA), 1989 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Estimated Agricultural Seasonal Hired Workers (New York State), 1973-1990 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey (No. 1, U.S. D.O.L.), 1990 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Atlas of Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers (U.S. Dept. of Health and Human Services), 1990 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Number of Migrant Farmworkers in New York State, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Hired and Contractual Labor in U.S. Agriculture - USDA, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Estimates of Migrant Farmworker Population in New York State, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - A Profile of Hired Farmworkers, 1992 - USDA, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey (No. 3, U.S. D.O.L), 1993 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - A Profile of United Stated Farmworkers (U.S. Department of Labor, based on NAWS), 1997 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Census 2000 and Migrant Farmworkers, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey (No. 8, U.S. D.O.L), 2000 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Findings from the National Agricultural Workers Survey (No. 9, U.S. D.O.L), 2005 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Migrant Enumeration Project - Migrant Legal Services, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Farmworker Numbers Estimates - Farmworker Legal Services Project (1) (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Farmworker Numbers Estimates - Farmworker Legal Services Project (2) (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Series XIX. Health Studies
  - Health Services for Migrant Children - Beverly Bove, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1973 Migrant Health Program Target Population Estimates, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Public Assistance...for Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers (New York State Social Services), 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Cost and Utilization Evaluation - Migrant Hospital Program, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Use Among Migrant Laborers - Richard Morales, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Oak Orchard Health Center Study and Subsequent Controversy, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Health Studies Background / Correspondence - Chi, White-Means, 1983-1989 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - New York Migrant Health Interview Surveys - Chi, White-Means, 1980-1989 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Needs and Economic Impact of Migrant Farmworkers (New York State), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Medical Utilization Patterns of Migrant Farmworkers (Wayne County New York), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Migrant Health Programs (New York State Migrant Education), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Migrant Parents' Descriptions of Health Problems, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Alcohol Consumption, Health Status and Economic Productivity Proposals, 1984-86 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - The Health Effects of Agricultural Production - Molly Joel Coye, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Infectious Diseases and Fieldwater...Among Migrant Farmworkers, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Health Status and Economic Productivity (Orange County New York), 1986 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Health Care for Migrants in New York State - Bureau of Health Resources, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Drinking, Farm and Camp Life - Chi and McClain, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund (Ann Hales Thesis), 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Ann Hales Research, 1986-92 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Statewide Need / Demand Assessment for Migrants...New York State Department of Health, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Statewide Strategies for Health Care for Migrants and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Ann Hales Thesis, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworker Health Objectives for the Year 2000, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Migrant Health Status and Utilization Patterns - Doris P. Slesinger, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Research on Migrant Farmworkers in New York State - Chi, White-Means, McClain, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Migrant Health Care in New York State (New York State Dept. of Health), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 27)